Cortex can now help with almost
everything.
But only if it can work where actual
work happens. And for many of us, that
place is Chrome. To help with that, we
just launched the Chrome extension for
Cortex. It works with the Cortex app in
both Windows and Mac OS. Let me show you
what you can actually do with it and how
it works with plugins and other ways
that you can connect Cortex to the tools
that you already use. If there's a
plugin for the app that I need, I
normally start there. Connectors are
structured and fast and Cortex does not
have to click through all the UI just to
read a doc or check a message or create
a file. Sometimes, however, there is no
plugin or there is one, but the thing
you need is only available in the full
web app. And sometimes the context is
actually the existing logged-in Chrome
session.
This is what the Chrome extension is
for. It lets Cortex work in your real
browser. Same profile, same session,
same cookies, same tabs, same logged-in
apps.
While the in-app browser is great for
local development tasks and giving
detailed feedback to Cortex using
annotations, the Chrome extension can
work across multiple tabs in parallel
and use many of the features of the real
browser. For example, I can have Cortex
do some research on the user sentiment
of our latest launches, identify new use
cases, highlight pain points, and then
take all of that and output it into an
actual spreadsheet.
Compared to regular computer use, Cortex
also won't take over my whole browser.
It creates its own Chrome tab group,
will work from there, and it can open
multiple tabs, scroll through pages, and
find content, and then reason along the
way to see if it has the correct course.
All in the background, so I can keep
working undisturbed in my own tabs.
Cortex can also combine it with other
plugins.
For example, to handle my expense
reports, it can check my emails using a
plugin, search for emails related to my
latest trip, extract all the relevant
information, and then fill out the
expense forms. It can even upload the
missing receipts directly from my
computer.
And because the extension can leverage
code execution, Codex can control Chrome
without the usual screenshot, reason,
move the mouse loop. It can script
repetitive work and even work in
multiple tabs in parallel.
For example, I've been working on this
multiplayer drawing game and I can have
Codex spin up individual sub agents that
play the game together. In this case,
each agent has their own browser tab to
play in so they can play in parallel and
collaborate on the game.
The Chrome extension lets you do more by
connecting Codex to the tools and apps
that you're already using. Give it a
try.